Hmm...not allowed
no no no go away
Go away...wait
Ah...
Hello everyone
I am Lucy
Welcome to my
ClassyChoice boutique selection
Today I am going to unbox a bag!
This bag is
one that I have unboxed on my channel before
and my friend has a different color one
I think this color
is also a favorite of many people
so I borrowed it from him to unbox for you to see
and I will also share how to style it with this bag
using 12 items to create outfits for my week of 7 days
Alright, first let's take a look at this bag
What kind of bag do you think it is based on its size
Mini Roulis pig nose bag
I have unboxed it in another video
A denim blue pig nose bag
And this one is golden brown
It is the same as the other one I unboxed
Denim blue pig nose bag
They all have white stitching
I think the design with white stitching is super pretty
Let me show you the leather in detail
It is also made of Evercolor leather
The shoulder strap is hidden inside
I will take it out to show you later
In the other unboxing video of the pig nose bag
I have already measured its length, width, and height
I introduced some details of this bag to everyone
So in this video
I won't repeat it again
In the previous video
I did not test its capacity for everyone to see
Some people say
They want to see the capacity of the pig nose bag
So now I'll use my friend's bag
to actually pack!
Let me show you
The main compartments inside look like this
There are two big compartments
And a small compartment in the middle
There is also a small compartment at the back of the bag
First, the phone
Wallet
My Calvi Duo
Antibacterial spray
Hand cream
Lip balm
Lipstick
Let me show you how it looks when it's all packed
Actually, it's still okay here
Let's add a cushion foundation
If we move the lipstick here
And there's also a little space here
This part is actually quite loose
If you move the things up
It's also fine
Then closing it won't be difficult.